<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Quotes>
<Quote>
<Author>Stokely Carmichael</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>There is a higher law than the law of government. That's the law of conscience</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Stormzy</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Even if you don't like me, you know me because I'm just in your face</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Sue Monk Kidd</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>People who think dying is the worst thing don't know a thing about life</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Sugar Ray Leonard</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>We're all given some sort of skill in life. Mine just happens to be beating up on people</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Sun Ra</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm not a minister, I'm not a philosopher, I'm not a politician, I'm in another category</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Susan B. Anthony</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>She who succeeds in gaining the mastery of the bicycle will gain the mastery of life</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Susan George</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>If you cut down a forest, it doesn't matter how many sawmills you have if there are no more trees</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Susan Sontag</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Travel becomes a strategy for accumulating photographs</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Suze Orman</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>When you are grateful - when you can see what you have - you unlock blessings to flow in your life</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Swami Sivananda</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Put your heart, mind, and soul into even your smallest acts. This is the secret of success</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Syd Barrett</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm disappearing, avoiding most things</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Sydney J. Harris</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The time to relax is when you don't have time for it</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Sylvester Stallone</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I believe any success in life is made by going into an area with a blind, furious optimism</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Sylvia Earle</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>No water, no life. No blue, no green</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I say, you work eight hours, and you sleep eight hours - be sure they're not the same eight hours</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Life is tragic and absurd, and none of it has any purpose at all</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>There's sketch, improv, writing, acting, music, and badminton. Those are the seven forms of comedy</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>T.I.</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm going to always rise above the doubt that may exist about me</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>T</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - I do understand how hate eats at the soul and how to purge yourself of hate</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tacitus</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>When men are full of envy they disparage everything, whether it be good or bad</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>There is a role and function for beauty in our time</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I didn't want to fall into the trap of complacency</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Skip the religion and politics, head straight to the compassion. Everything else is a distraction</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>If I had to live my life again, I'd make the same mistakes, only sooner</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>As a woman, I believe you have to embrace your body, and feel beautiful both inside and out</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm Irish on St. Patrick's Day. I'm Italian on Columbus Day. I'm a New Yorker every day</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I spent a lot of time between bars like this</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>At the end of the day, I stand by who I am. I'm a good person</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Times have changed; so must the lenses through which we see the political future</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Trust your gut. You know yourself, so don't let somebody else tell you who you are</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I think that everybody wants to be heard, and the easiest way to be the loudest is to be the hater</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I've learned that when God promises beauty through the ashes, He means it</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm not the biggest motorcycle fan - they're cool and a lot of fun, but they're scary as well!</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Be yourself. You're okay. And it really doesn't matter what other people think</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>My touchstone for every question is the Constitution</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Vegetarians are cool. All I eat are vegetarians - except for the occasional mountain lion steak</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The typical output deal from a studio is 10 to 14 movies a year</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ted Turner</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>You can never quit. Winners never quit, and quitters never win</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ted Williams</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>If you don't think too good, don't think too much</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Teller</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm more apt to cry at something beautiful than at something sad</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Temple Grandin</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I cannot emphasize enough the importance of a good teacher</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tennessee Williams</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The only thing worse than a liar is a liar that's also a hypocrite!</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Terence</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>They are so knowing, that they know nothing</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Teri Garr</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Take a step back, evaluate what is important, and enjoy life</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Terry Eagleton</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Evil is often supposed to be without rhyme or reason</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Terry Pratchett</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>In ancient times cats were worshipped as gods; they have not forgotten this</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Terry Wogan</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Nobody really knows what they look like. The mirror shows you only what you want to see</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thalia</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Since I was little, I've had that vision of a businesswoman inside me</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>The Notorious B.I.G.</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I hold grudges, but I can't hate nobody; that's not my nature</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>The Weeknd</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I make good music for long journeys</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Theodor Adorno</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Freedom would be not to choose between black and white but to abjure such prescribed choices</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Theophilus London</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Shopping at any level is a bit of therapy for my medulla oblongata</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Theresa May</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>In tough times, everyone has to take their share of the pain</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thom Mayne</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The huge problem in our society is the enormous ignorance of the ideas that underlie modern art</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thom Tillis</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>'Intensity' is a good word. It's like ambition, if it's not ambition at expense of someone else</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thom Yorke</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Sometimes the nicest thing to do with a guitar is just look at it</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas a Kempis</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>First keep peace with yourself, then you can also bring peace to others</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Babington Macaulay</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Nothing except the mint can make money without advertising</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Dekker</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Sleep is that golden chain that ties health and our bodies together</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Friedman</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>There is no substitute for face-to-face reporting and research</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Fuller</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>If you have one true friend you have more than your share</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Gibson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I work in show business - there's nothing that shocks me anymore!</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Hardy</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Time changes everything except something within us which is always surprised by change</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Hobbes</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Words are the money of fools</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Huxley</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The great thing in the world is not so much to seek happiness as to earn peace and self-respect</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas J. Watson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The great accomplishments of man have resulted from the transmission of ideas and enthusiasm</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Keller</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>We go through our careers and things happen to us. Those experiences made me what I am</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Kinkade</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Art is forever</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Mann</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>People's behavior makes sense if you think about it in terms of their goals, needs, and motives</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Moore</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The heart that has truly loved never forgets, But as truly loves on to the close</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas P. O'Neill</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>It's easier to run for office than to run the office</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Rhett</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm not just trying to be good at one thing and then call it a day. I want to be like Bruno Mars</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas S. Monson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Choose your friends with caution; plan your future with purpose, and frame your life with faith</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Thomas Szasz</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Boredom is the feeling that everything is a waste of time; serenity, that nothing is</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tia Mowry</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>There's nobody in the world that knows me better than my sister</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tiger Shroff</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I am not at all stylish. For me, style is a state of mind and individuality</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tiger Woods</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Achievements on the golf course are not what matters, decency and honesty are what matter</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tila Tequila</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>My fans and people who know of my character want to see me become more successful</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Allen</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm a creative guy, artistically with graphics</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Berner</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>ee - We need diversity of thought in the world to face the new challenges</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Burton</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Visions are worth fighting for. Why spend your life making someone else's dreams?</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Cook</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Life is fragile. We're not guaranteed a tomorrow so give it everything you've got</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Curry</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I remember candy rationing until I was, like, 7</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Gunn</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Does a man need to know what a peplum is? Probably not</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Howard</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>In the end, very little gets in the way of what Manchester United wants to do</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim O'Brien</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Laughter does not deny pain. Laughter - like a wail - acknowledges and replies to pain</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Ryan</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>If you're a quarterback and you keep throwing interceptions, you change quarterbacks</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Tebow</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'll always use the negativity as more motivation to work even harder and become even stronger</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tim Vine</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I went out on a date with Simile. I don't know what I metaphor</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Timothy Leary</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>You can always pick up your needle and move to another groove</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Timothy Noah</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The U.S. policy of hoarding crude oil never made the world, or even the U.S., a safer place</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tina Brown</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The Taliban knows they have more to fear from an educated girl than an American drone</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tina Fey</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Being a mom has made me so tired. And so happy</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tink</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The key to artistry is being able to say stuff the way other people can't</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tippi Hedren</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Birds I am fine with - spiders are an entirely different matter</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tituss Burgess</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I hover closer to earth than I do the clouds</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Todd Phillips</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Bangkok, like Las Vegas, sounds like a place where you make bad decisions</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Todd Rundgren</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I never thought a Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in Cleveland or anywhere else was a good idea</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Araya</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>When I do interviews, I enter them with an open mind and try to answer the questions the best I can</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Baker</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I wasn't interested in novelty. I was looking for good drama</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Brokaw</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>It's easy to make a buck. It's a lot tougher to make a difference</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Clancy</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The objective of a terrorist is to create political change in the society he targets</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Cotton</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I don't do stairs. And I don't do groups</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Cruise</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I disagree with people who think you learn more from getting beat up than you do from winning</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom DeLonge</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I always want to do different things. I'm always obsessed with trying to do different things</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Douglas</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Sweet, delicious Dungeness crab is always a treat</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Felton</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I like to fish. Fishing is always a way of relaxing</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Ford</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I probably do have an obsessive personality, but striving for perfection has served me well</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Hanks</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>A hero is somebody who voluntarily walks into the unknown</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Hodgkinson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>When the going gets tough, the tough take a nap</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Landry</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>A winner never stops trying</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Lehrer</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Be prepared, and be careful not to do your good deeds when there's no one watching you</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Peters</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>If a window of opportunity appears, don't pull down the shade</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Rath</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Making better choices takes work. There is a daily give and take, but it is worth the effort</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Robbins</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>We're our own dragons as well as our own heroes, and we have to rescue ourselves from ourselves</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Selleck</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I live a pretty simple life</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Shadyac</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I think true success is intrinsic... It's love. It's kindness. It's community</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Stoppard</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>If you carry your childhood with you, you never become older</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Waits</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Don't you know there ain't no devil, it's just god when he's drunk</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Wilson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>A smile is happiness you'll find right under your nose</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tom Wolfe</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The surest cure for vanity is loneliness</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tommy Chong</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>But you can't exercise and be high. It's impossible</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tommy Hilfiger</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I think it's dangerous to think that you're successful, because then you become complacent</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tommy Lasorda</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a man's determination</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tommy Lee</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm really a cool, mellow guy. I'm not as crazy as everybody thinks</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tommy Lee Jones</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The world's not a very comfortable place if you have a nightmare to face</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tommy Wiseau</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I inspire myself</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Toni Morrison</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>All water has a perfect memory and is forever trying to get back to where it was</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tony Abbott</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I would not want to see any relaxation of the law prohibiting human cloning</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tony Blair</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Sometimes it is better to lose and do the right thing than to win and do the wrong thing</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tony Campolo</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Of the 22 industrialized nations of the world, we're dead last in per capita giving to poor people</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tony Dungy</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The best leaders are following Christ. That's the best leader you can follow</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tony Scott</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I have a short attention span</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tori Amos</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Being stylish is about enjoying your life and expressing yourself and your inner light</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tory Burch</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I never go out during the day without sunglasses</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tory Lanez</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The way that I learned to be confident was I would ride the back of the city bus and sing very low</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tracee Ellis Ross</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I am a connoisseur of products. I check out everything, I try everything</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tracey Emin</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I don't ask for an apology because it's only tomorrow's fish-and-chip paper</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tracy Morgan</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I think the word 'pregnant' is funny</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Travis Barker</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Thank you for life, and all the little ups and downs that make it worth living</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Travis Kalanick</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Ultimately, progress and innovation win</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Travis Scott</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>There's a lot of us out here that are birds, man. We all need to just fly</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Trent Reznor</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>In my nothing, you were everything, to me</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Trey Anastasio</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I've always loved the experience of working together with other people toward an artistic goal</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Trey Gowdy</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>You may be less likely to pick on someone if you don't know what's in their briefcase or purse</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Trey Parker</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The problem is we moved to LA... The only way to be punk rock in L.A. is to be a Republican</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Trisha Yearwood</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>What's meant to be will always find a way</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Troy Polamalu</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>When I let my hair down, I just let it down. It's more comfortable in my helmet</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Truman Capote</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Venice is like eating an entire box of chocolate liqueurs in one go</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tucker Carlson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>To be a feminist, you could cut your hair really short. You have to be really angry about something</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tucker Max</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The haters always scream the loudest</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Twiggy</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Fashion should be stylish and fun</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Twinkle Khanna</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>To me, a life that doesn't change things and touch people's lives is pretty meaningless</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Twyla Tharp</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Dance is the most fundamental of all art forms</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ty Dolla Sign</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>If something's dope, you got to go with it</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tyga</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The best career advice I've gotten is to stay focused, keep moving forward</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tyler Perry</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I love to give. I've been a giver all my life</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Tyra Banks</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I love the confidence that makeup gives me</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Uday Kotak</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I am a believer in the journey and enjoying the journey</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ulysses S. Grant</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>My failures have been errors in judgment, not of intent</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Uma Thurman</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Tall, sandy blonde, with sort of blue eyes, skinny in places, fat in others. An average gal</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Umberto Eco</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The real hero is always a hero by mistake; he dreams of being an honest coward like everybody else</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Unknown</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The past cannot be changed. The future is yet in your power</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ursula Andress</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>This bikini made me a success</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ursula K. Le Guin</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>To light a candle is to cast a shadow</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Usain Bolt</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>A lot of legends, a lot of people, have come before me. But this is my time</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Usher</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm a flamboyant type of guy, a cooler version of Liberace</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Uta Hagen</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I won't go to England because they won't let my dog in</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Utada Hikaru</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm not like a gorgeous bombshell or anything like that</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Uwe Boll</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Interview with a Vampire was lots of sex, so I'm not sure</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>V. S. Naipaul</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>It is important not to trust people too much</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Val Kilmer</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Without deadlines and restrictions I just tend to become preoccupied with other things</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Valentino Rossi</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Riding a race bike is an art - a thing that you do because you feel something inside</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Valerie Bertinelli</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Honesty is very sexy</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vanessa Bayer</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>There are just so many funny kids and teenagers. They're just not aware of how funny they are</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vanessa Hudgens</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Being cool is being your own self, not doing something that someone else is telling you to do</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vanessa Mae</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I will be the Thai equivalent of Eddie the Eagle</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vanessa Paradis</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Life is like the ocean, it goes up and down</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vanilla Ice</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I don't have any reason to hate anybody; I believe in good karma and spreading good energy</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vanity</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Every day, I wake up and say, 'Good Morning, Jesus.'</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Venus Williams</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I don't focus on what I'm up against. I focus on my goals and I try to ignore the rest</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vera Farmiga</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm part wood nymph. I require mountains and warm, dense patches of moss to thrive</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vera Wang</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Success isn't about the end result, it's about what you learn along the way</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Verne Troyer</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Doing stunt work is risky, but it's something I enjoy</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vernon Howard</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>You have succeeded in life when all you really want is only what you really need</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vicente Fox</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Instead of building walls, we should be building bridges</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vicki Lawrence</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>That's my opportunity to hide behind that old lady and say what I want to say</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victor Cruz</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I've had the same barber since I was about 14 years old</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victor Garber</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Being on a television series is sort of life-altering on every level</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victor LaValle</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Lonely women destroy themselves; lonely men threaten the world</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victor Ponta</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Romania strongly supports Turkey's E.U. accession</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Abril</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Keep your ears open, your eyes open, grab everything you can, react, and learn!</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Azarenka</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>My grandmother is the person who inspires me the most</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Beckham</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I have always loved fashion since I was a kid and customized my school uniforms</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Jackson</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I always dreamed of being Maria in The Sound of Music</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Justice</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>It's nice to just embrace the natural beauty within you</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Moran</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm not perfect, but what's wonderful about eating a plant-based diet is, I don't have to be</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Pendleton</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I worried I was a boyish shape. I always thought I might grow some, but it never happened</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Pratt</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I came to acting in a very circuitous way</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Principal</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I went to a woman for advice about how to be in business, but I learned a great deal from men</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Victoria Woodhull</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>While others prayed for the good time coming, I worked for it</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vidal Sassoon</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>It's okay saying sorry, but when you are drunk you say what you really feel</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vidya Balan</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I think a woman should be wholesome, voluptuous and sizzling!</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Viggo Mortensen</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I like stories that leave you wanting more, leave you wondering, but don't tell you everything</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vijay Mallya</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I live the way I want to live, and I don't comment on the way that other people live</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vikas Swarup</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The slums are not a place of despair. Its inhabitants are all working towards a better life</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vikram Seth</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The thing about inspiration is that it takes your mind off everything else</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Viktor Orban</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The best migrant is the migrant who does not come</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ville Valo</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Art is always criticized and always an outsider gets the blame</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vince Flynn</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I'm a bit of a Libertarian</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vince McMahon</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The biggest thrill in the world is entertaining the public, there is no bigger thrill than that</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vince Staples</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>When I was growing up, skateboarding was big and basketball was big</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vince Vaughn</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Whenever you're scared of something, don't let that define you. We all feel it, but step up</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vincent Bugliosi</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>This is America, not a banana republic</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vincent Cassel</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The minute I started being recognised, I became much more discreet</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vincent D'Onofrio</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>And I have been able to establish this sort of decent reputation as being a decent character actor</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vincente Minnelli</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Color can do anything that black-and-white can</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Ving Rhames</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The more you do a stunt, the more you increase the risk of something happening</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vinnie Jones</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I've always had my ear pierced with a diamond stud. I did it myself when I was 16</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vinny Guadagnino</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Nobody wants to be a lawyer - it's hard work. But it was kind of my academic route</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vint Cerf</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Although I've had several major career changes, I was extremely hesitant about making some of them</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Virat Kohli</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Self-belief and hard work will always earn you success</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Virgil Goode</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>All of us who serve in the House of Representatives and the Senate pay into Social Security</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Virginia Postrel</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Storage problems make neon signs the most ephemeral of commercial arts</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vittorio Alfieri</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Deep vengeance is the daughter of deep silence</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vivien Leigh</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Dear Lord, I'm so grateful I'm still loved</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vivienne Ming</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>What drives success, and the most successful students, is internal motivation</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vivienne Westwood</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I can't think without my glasses</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vladimir Horowitz</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>My future is in my past and my past is my present. I must now make the present my future</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vladimir Zhirinovsky</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>A mother-in-law is better than a single and childless political persona, though</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Vonda Shepard</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I had a hard-core cult following of at least 12</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>W. Clement Stone</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Aim for the moon. If you miss, you may hit a star</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>W. H. Auden</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>We are all here on earth to help others; what on earth the others are here for I don't know</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>W. Somerset Maugham</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Every production of an artist should be the expression of an adventure of his soul</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Wale</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>My job is to inspire the people, to be on top of my game and push my culture forward</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Wallace Shawn</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I spend most of my time thinking about things like laundry and buying stationery supplies</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Wallace Stevens</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The most beautiful thing in the world is, of course, the world itself</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walt Mossberg</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I try not to make snap judgments. I never, ever make conclusions about products I've never tried</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Annenberg</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Never buy four C-plus paintings when you can buy one A</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Bagehot</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>The greatest mistake is trying to be more agreeable than you can be</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Benjamin</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Counsel woven into the fabric of real life is wisdom</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Cronkite</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I can't imagine a person becoming a success who doesn't give this game of life everything he's got</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Dean Myers</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>I like people who take responsibility for their lives</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Jon Williams</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>How long it takes to write a book depends on its length</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Lang</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Time was God's first creation</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Lippmann</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>When men can no longer be theists, they must, if they are civilized, become humanists</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter O'Brien</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Hacking involves a different way of looking at problems that no one's thought of</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Savage Landor</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>Men, like nails, lose their usefulness when they lose their direction and begin to bend</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Scott</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>For success, attitude is equally as important as ability</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
<Quote>
<Author>Walter Winchell</Author>
<Language>English</Language>
<QuoteValue>A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out</QuoteValue>
</Quote>
</Quotes>

