<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Quotes>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Once people tell me I can't do stuff, I'm going to go and make it happen</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I love vintage cars because you can do so much more to them</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm a fan of Jay-Z, I'mma always be a fan of Jay-Z</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>We must all learn to adjust with our surroundings</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>'Nappy' is a state of mind, not an appearance</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't do the whole, 'Put my name on it, make me famous' thing</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Doing voice-over work is something that I love to do, and it is a lot of fun at the same time</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm still a person, a human being, no matter what religion I am</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T-Pain</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm pretty much in love with 'Adult Swim.'</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I say, you work eight hours, and you sleep eight hours - be sure they're not the same eight hours</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I think I have more patience now than I did in the past</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The cheapest natural gas in the world is in the United States</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>On a scale from 1-10, my ambition is probably 11 or 12</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If somebody I don't like gets in the crosshairs, I pull the trigger. But I don't hunt for them</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Fundamentals make the market</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I always saw myself as a large stockholder trying to make a difference. I wasn't raiding anybody</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Work eight hours and sleep eight hours and make sure that they are not the same hours</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If you don't have a refinery operating, it's hard to use oil that's available</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. Boone Pickens</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If you can provide the funding and you get the leadership, you'll have a competitive team</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Life is tragic and absurd, and none of it has any purpose at all</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>This is the beauty of fiction. We may not like these characters, but we inhabit them</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm enslaved to writing to the point where I sacrifice almost everything else</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>As humans, we all want our own island. Of course, the truth is, we're never going to get it</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I love performing in front of an audience. I like the questions; I like controversy</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Sometimes, we find common ground; more often, we don't</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>You want, as an artist, to be pushing yourself to do what you haven't done before</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I really like the power of stopping the laughter and turning it to horror</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I've always written about heroes and wondered who they are</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. C. Boyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>What is your identity, and how do you know who you are if you don't have language?</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>There's sketch, improv, writing, acting, music, and badminton. Those are the seven forms of comedy</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't sit and write stand-up material; I come up with an idea onstage</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Life is hard. Not great. Kind of tragic</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I have perfectly symmetrical ankles</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I laugh at absurdity hardest, then stories, then observations, then bearded men on roller skates</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I do like the idea of being an auteur in the sense of writing and being in your own stuff</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Everybody asks me what it was like to be in my underwear for my network television debut</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I drink a fair amount of ramen noodles</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't know how much the economy has changed since Jonathan Swift's 'A Modest Proposal.'</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T. J. Miller</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>It is good to connect to someone who reminds you that you have some real authenticity</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm going to always rise above the doubt that may exist about me</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>It goes without saying that it's hard to attain a certain level of success</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Danger is ever-present in life, more for some than others</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I, myself, I am not interested in reality television; just me, myself, speaking</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Nobody is gonna love you like you. You're gonna be your best salesman</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Everyone has something to sell. The greatest thing you can ever sell is an idea or talent</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I've learned that one thing about my life that is certain is trouble</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm an honest, open father</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My father passed away in 2002, but yes, we were pretty close. I loved him a lot</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T.I.</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I love BET and I love the fans</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - I do understand how hate eats at the soul and how to purge yourself of hate</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - We are all losers in comparison to Malala Yousafzai. But we are not all geniuses. Like me</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - I love America the way I love my family - I was born into it. And there's no escape out of it</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - The country in which reparations actually happen is a very different one than the one we live in</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - I'm not going to break up my family, not for a book</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - You can oppose reparations all you want, but you got to know the facts. You really, really do</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - My dad always associated information with liberation. He was very much in that Malcolm X tradition</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - I was born in West Baltimore, lived in a situation in which violence was everywhere</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - Racism is a physical experience</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>T</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>ehisi Coates - It's kind of selfish to say that you're only going to fight for a victory that you will live to see</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>When men are full of envy they disparage everything, whether it be good or bad</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>When the state is most corrupt, then the laws are most multiplied</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Old things are always in good repute, present things in disfavor</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The more corrupt the state, the more numerous the laws</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Truth is confirmed by inspection and delay; falsehood by haste and uncertainty</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>A desire to resist oppression is implanted in the nature of man</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>To show resentment at a reproach is to acknowledge that one may have deserved it</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Reason and judgment are the qualities of a leader</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>It belongs to human nature to hate those you have injured</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tacitus</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Victor and vanquished never unite in substantial agreement</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>There is a role and function for beauty in our time</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I believe that the way people live can be directed a little by architecture</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I would like my architecture to inspire people to use their own resources, to move into the future</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If you give people nothingness, they can ponder what can be achieved from that nothingness</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My hand is the extension of the thinking process - the creative process</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The speed of change makes you wonder what will become of architecture</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>When I draw something, the brain and the hands work together</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>In Japan, there is less a culture of preserving old buildings than in Europe</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>All architecture has a public nature, I believe, so I would like to make a public space</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tadao Ando</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If there is only one culture all over the world, that's not a good thing</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I didn't want to fall into the trap of complacency</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My parents grew up during the Harlem renaissance</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I pretty much move around wherever I like</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm always cracking up when I hear what people think I should be doing</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm doing exactly what I always wanted to do, and I still like what I can do musically</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My music is really fun music, with some pan-African and pan-American influences</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Particularly with the blues, it's not just about bad times. It's about the healing spirit</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Music is like the soul of the planet</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>What the future of the planet and music and art and all of it is sharing; it's diversity</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taj Mahal</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I wanted to explore the connections between different kinds of music</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Skip the religion and politics, head straight to the compassion. Everything else is a distraction</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Hip-hop isn't as complex as a woman is</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I will never do a record without some sense of responsibility</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Woman are complex creatures</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I think hip hop is a dance music that's rebellious by nature</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>That's what hip-hop is: It's sociology and English put to a beat, you know</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If I'm performing with a DJ, it's all on me to draw the energy. I like the camaraderie of a band</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Things are fluid in this world, and if you don't remain fluid, you get lost in the sauce</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>And you know, art as commerce, doesn't really make too much sense, they don't go together</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Talib Kweli</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>But it becomes disrespectful when the artist's process is not respected</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If I had to live my life again, I'd make the same mistakes, only sooner</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'd rather be strongly wrong than weakly right</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My heart is as pure as the driven slush</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>It's the good girls who keep diaries; the bad girls never have the time</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I read Shakespeare and the Bible, and I can shoot dice. That's what I call a liberal education</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Nobody can be exactly like me. Even I have trouble doing it</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Only good girls keep diaries. Bad girls don't have time</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If you really want to help the American theater, don't be an actress, dahling. Be an audience</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Acting is a form of confession</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tallulah Bankhead</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>There is less in this than meets the eye</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>As a woman, I believe you have to embrace your body, and feel beautiful both inside and out</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Id rather have a fake smile than a nasty stare</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My boyfriend thinks it's crazy that I wear a different bikini every day on holiday</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>On my foot it says, 'The best is yet to come,' and that's there because I really believe it</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Not every woman has time to go to a salon and have her hair blow-dried every day</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>When you are rich, people try to take advantage of you</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Everyone has a past, and the downside to my life is that the past gets dragged up</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Before mobile phones, I used to call my parents from a phone box and reverse the charges</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Formula One has been the backdrop of my life</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Ecclestone</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My parents are opposites who balance each other out</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm Irish on St. Patrick's Day. I'm Italian on Columbus Day. I'm a New Yorker every day</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I believe that you can always learn from observation</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I've been in this business a long time, and I'm very clear on what is real and what is fleeting</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I always watch the work I do</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Chuck Cooper is a friend, and I adore him. He can do so many things</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I am always happy to use my song and dance training</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I want to play Eva Peron. I've already done a lot of Shakespeare, but I'd like to do Lady Macbeth</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I've always come into a show when the show was already up and running</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I have Native American blood. I have African blood. I have European blood</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tamara Tunie</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I grew up in a funeral home. Both my parents were morticians</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I spent a lot of time between bars like this</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I shouldn't even be here, so if I'm here, I better do something good</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The power of the ADA is that it ended up changing my life long before I ever imagined it would</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The ADA allows persons with disabilities the opportunity to participate in the world around them</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My arm bones looked like chicken bones</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If I still had my legs, I would be in line for a battalion command, and instead, I'm flying a desk</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Running for Senate is a very involved process</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't ever want to be sad about my life</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I always wanted to be an ambassador</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tammy Duckworth</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'd do anything to help veterans</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>At the end of the day, I stand by who I am. I'm a good person</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Once you're a mom, always a mom. It's like riding a bike, you never forget</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Love is the greatest gift that God has given us. It's free</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm always the cousin that can't make it to the family functions because I'm busy</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I just like when I work with people that are professional and good</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I feel like we all have our skeletons</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm always interested in challenging myself and pushing and seeing how far I can go</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm really silly. That's the thing that people don't get</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm a creative person, so I have to stay busy</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taraji P. Henson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm nothing without God</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Times have changed; so must the lenses through which we see the political future</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The rich stick together; the poor and the marginalised are thrown together</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Ramadan is, in its essence, a month of humanist spirituality</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The process of reclaiming the self is one of reconciliation with meaning</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Clarity and consistency are not enough: the quest for truth requires humility and effort</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Lack of consistency is a weakness shared by all nations</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I want to be an activist professor</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>In its haste to bolster nationalism, in its obsession with security, Europe is losing its soul</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Every country in Europe needs immigrants for its economic survival</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tariq Ramadan</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Political rhetoric leads only to confusion</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Trust your gut. You know yourself, so don't let somebody else tell you who you are</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>How you go about moving within the world you live in says so much about who you are</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>There's something about music that makes me feel like a different person, that feels like an escape</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Sex isn't hard, but intimacy is terrifying</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm a huge 'Futurama' fan, so that's my closest sci-fi tendency</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I love hip-hop; I love Sleigh Bells. I also love classical music and musical theater</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>It's always been my dream to just continually do really cool indie movies - character-driven stuff</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I think being idle is quite hard for me to do</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The way people love sci-fi is how I love cartoons</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tatiana Maslany</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I fell in love with 'Star Trek' after J. J. Abrams's movie. I'm so into that</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I think that everybody wants to be heard, and the easiest way to be the loudest is to be the hater</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The idea that feeling confident and feeling misunderstood are mutually exclusive really bugs me</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Half of my closet is Barbie clothes - PVC skirts, cropped fuzzy sweaters, and velvet minis</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I think it'd be great to own a fun concept store with my friends and just sell books and records</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Oh God, I'm awful at sports. In gym I just try and avoid getting hit in the face</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>One thing that I always liked about fashion was that it was tied in with music and art and film</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I try not to do anything I don't like, so I stay motivated pretty easily</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>You like the style of the people you like because it reflects something inside them</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I would like to write a movie and, if it wasn't too crazy, also direct</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Tavi Gevinson</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I love 'First Wives Club' and 'Death Becomes Her' and movies about women like that</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I've learned that when God promises beauty through the ashes, He means it</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I think it's a mistake to miss out on joy just because you have pain</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>In your darkest moments of despair, a friend's hand on yours will get you through the worst</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>You like to be independent, but you will need to learn to ask for help. It doesn't make you weak</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The only way to defeat evil is by taking advantage of our freedoms</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm not a fan of people romanticizing their loved ones in death</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't move away from grief, rather through it</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>There's a consequence for everything, and that goes back to the Bible for me</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I have learned in my life that my plans don't matter. It's God's plan</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taya Kyle</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>You can forgive somebody and still believe they need a consequence</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm not the biggest motorcycle fan - they're cool and a lot of fun, but they're scary as well!</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>You've got to keep your eye on the prize and do what you love to do</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I love to have fun and goof around and be silly, so anybody who can also do that is good for me</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I am that weirdo that chooses the difficult route down the side of the street</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>'Braveheart' is way up there for me</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm a big fan of all those singing competition shows</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I do love traveling, so I've been able to travel a lot</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If you constantly pound your muscles, they'll never have time to repair</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I got the famous Oprah hug!</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Lautner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>There's no ex out there who I'm not friends with today, and I'm extremely thankful for that</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Be yourself. You're okay. And it really doesn't matter what other people think</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm really into Greek yogurt, fruit and almonds. Those are my 'go-to' snacks</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Coffee makes me go crazy</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't know my armpit from my elbow in Los Angeles</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Whatever it is that I am working on is what I become obsessed with</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm the girl who will show up in jeans no matter what - but the jeans can get fancier and fancier</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't do detoxes or cleanses; they don't really work for me</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I like to do yoga, Pilates, dance, and things like that</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>'The Notebook' is one of my favorite love stories</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Taylor Schilling</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't have a connection to the fashion world at all</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My touchstone for every question is the Constitution</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>It took Jimmy Carter to give us Ronald Reagan</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>What Obamacare does is decreases choices and drives up cost</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I was bitten by an octopus</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If you hate the Jewish people, you are not reflecting the teachings of Christ</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I've spent the past month in Washington, D.C., and it is terrific to be back in America</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>In both law and politics, I think the essential battle is the meta-battle of framing the narrative</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm not serving in office because I desperately needed 99 new friends in the U.S. Senate</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The power of the American people, when we rise up and stand for liberty, knows no bounds</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Cruz</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>It's tragic from how far we've come from 'Hope and Change'</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Vegetarians are cool. All I eat are vegetarians - except for the occasional mountain lion steak</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I surround myself with positive, productive people of good will and decency</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If there is one thing I am, it's always right</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I hump the wild to take it all in, there is no bag limit on happiness</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I'm the gun guy, a loud guitar Dirty Harry with a ponytail</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I have self-actualized. Pardon me whilst I adjust my glowing halo</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Use your lives wisely, my friends, and conserve these precious freedoms for future generations</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Without question Gibson guitars are the finest, most revered guitars on the planet</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>At 62, I remain clean and sober and my ponytail remains erect</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Nugent</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Hopping the fence or wading the Rio Grande River isn't part of America's immigration process</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>The typical output deal from a studio is 10 to 14 movies a year</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I love, personally, the experience of going to the theater, going to the cinema</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>We're closer to HBO than we are to the entire grid of cable on demand</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't want to kill windowing; I want to restore choice and options</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>There's no such thing as 'too much TV,' unless we're all spending more and not watching more</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Adam Sandler is a remarkable movie brand</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't think on-demand brings anything extra to sports</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>'Orange Is the New Black' and 'Sense8' have enjoyed great success all over the world</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>We are anxious and open to all forms of doing business in China</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Sarandos</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I don't know that on-demand sports is remarkably better than live sports</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>You can never quit. Winners never quit, and quitters never win</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I know what I'm having 'em put on my tombstone: 'I have nothing more to say'</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>My son is now an 'entrepreneur.' That's what you're called when you don't have a job</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Sports is like a war without the killing</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Just because your ratings are bigger doesn't mean you're better</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>All my life people have said that I wasn't going to make it</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If I only had a little humility, I'd be perfect</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>I didn't get here for my acting... but I love show business</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>There's nothing wrong with being fired</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Turner</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>Life is a game. Money is how we keep score</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <Author>Ted Williams</Author>
    <Language>English</Language>
    <QuoteValue>If you don't think too good, don't think too much</QuoteValue>
  </Quote>
</Quotes>

